<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OrbitFingers</string>
    <string name="main_menu_message">OrbitFingers</string>
    <string name="simple">Level 1</string>
    <string name="simple2">Level 2</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Sound</string>
    <string name="SOF">LEVEL </string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-6002737231550640/7399190413</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="how_to">How-To</string>
    <string name="empty">       </string>
    <string name="current_level_tv">Current Level: </string>
    <string name="target_score_tv">Target Score:   </string>
    <string name="min_score_tv">Minimum Score: </string>
    <string name="min">MIN</string>
    <string name="penalty_tv">Penalty:       </string>
    <string name="peak_score_tv">PEAK SCORE</string>
    <string name="reset">RESET</string>
    <string name="set_peak_min">SET MINIMUM TO PEAK (SMP) </string>
    <string name="set_peak_min_text">SMPs Remaining: </string>
    <string name="spacer">^^^^^_______^^^^^</string>
    <string name="x">X</string>
    <string name="level_2">NEXT L2</string>
    <string name="level_3">NEXT L3</string>
    <string name="level_4">NEXT L4</string>
    <string name="level_5">NEXT L5</string>
    <string name="peak_text">PEAK</string>
    <string name="level_string">LEVEL #</string>
    <string name="login_register">Login / Register</string>
    <string name="peak_score">Peak Score:</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="username">USERNAME</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="r_password">Re-Enter Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="register_here">Register Here</string>
    <string name="name">NAME</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="reg">Register:</string>
    <string name="min_score">Min Score:</string>
    <string name="smps_remaining">SMPs Remaining:</string>
    <string name="val">VAL</string>
    <string name="device">Device</string>
    <string name="server">Server</string>
    <string name="set">SET</string>
    <string name="load_save">Load / Save</string>
    <string name="position">RANKING:</string>
    <string name="level">Level:</string>
    <string name="not_available">LOADING</string>
    <string name="tied">T</string>
    <string name="top_five">TOP 5</string>
    <string name="title_activity_top_ten">TopTenActivity</string>
    <string name="one"  >1</string>
    <string name="two"  >2</string>
    <string name="three">3</string>
    <string name="four" >4</string>
    <string name="five" >5</string>
    <string name="message">Enter Your Display Message</string>
    <string name="set_message">Set Message</string>
    <string name="set_ranking_message">Set Ranking Message</string>
    <string name="rank">Rank:</string>
    <string name="user_name">Username:</string>
    <string name="peak_txt">Peak:</string>
    <string name="msg_txt">Message:</string>
    <string name="T">T</string>
    <string name="SMPs">SMPs:</string>
    <string name="multi">|MULTI|</string>
    <string name="arrow">></string>
    <string name="load">LOADING</string>
    <string name="reg_message">Values To Be Registered:</string>
    <string name="on">ON</string>
    <string name="off">OFF</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="alert_1">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tHOW TO PLAY:
        \n
        \nThe goal of OrbitFingers is to get the highest possible Peak Score and to be ranked in the
        TOP 5. The players who have the five highest Peak Scores will have their Usernames and
        Ranking Messages shown in the Top 5 Display.
        \nThe game contains a Left and a Right Orbit System which are independent but can only
        be activated one at a time. Click the left / right finger print area when the applicable
        Orbit System is in alignment to gain  10 points. There are two types of alignments:
        \n
        \n1: The static center is at the beginning of system alignment.
        \n
        \n2: The static center is in the middle of system alignment.
        \n
        \nThere is a penalty in points for activating the finger prints while the appropriate Orbit
        System is not aligned. Points will be deducted until the current Min Score is reached. The
        Min Score starts at zero and gets automatically set when a new Level is reached. The Min
        Score can also be manually set to the same value as the Peak Score by clicking the SMP
        button. The amount of times the SMP can be used is limited, however SMPs can be gained with
        each new Level and also by getting nine consecutive hits. When each new Level is unlocked
        the allowed margin of error is reduced and the rotation speed is increased.
        \n
        \nLevel\t\t\tMin Score\t\t\tPenalty\t\t\tSMPs
        \n\t\t1\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t0\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t-1\t\t\t\t\t\t\t+1
        \n\t\t2\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t100\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t-5\t\t\t\t\t\t\t+1
        \n\t\t3\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t300\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t-10\t\t\t\t\t\t+2
        \n\t\t4\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t600\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t-15\t\t\t\t\t\t+2
        \n\t\t5\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t1000\t\t\t\t\t\t\t-20\t\t\t\t\t\t+5
        \n
        \nClick the Login / Register Button to Login and set your Device Values to the previously
        saved Server Values or click the Register Link to sign up and register the current Device
        Values. Once Logged-in the Player can update the Server Values and get the Current Rank
        including the Top 5 Display. If the player is ranked in the Top 5, their Username and
        adjustable Ranking Message will be displayed.
    </string>
    <string name="alert_2">
        \nAre you sure? All unsaved Device Values will be LOST and / or the User will be LOGGED OUT.
    </string>
    <string name="smp_equal">Minimum And Peak Already Equal</string>
    <string name="tou">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="back">BACK</string>
    <string name="mismatch">Passwords Don\'t Match</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="reg_fail">Register Failed</string>
    <string name="no_ic">No Internet Connection</string>
    <string name="login_fail">Login Failed</string>
    <string name="agree">I AGREE</string>
    <string name="not_agree">I DO NOT AGREE</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_actual">Privacy Policy
        \n
        \nLast updated: July 18, 2017
        \n
        \nPoloApps ("us", "we", or "our") operates the OrbitFingers mobile application (the
        "Service").
        \nThis page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of
        Personal Information when you use our Service. We will not use or share your information
        with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
        \nWe use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the
        Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
        Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the
        same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.
        \n
        \nInformation Collection And Use:
        \n
        \nWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable
        information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information
        may include, but is not limited to, your name ("Personal Information").
        \nWe collect this information for the purpose of providing the Service, identifying and
        communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase
        orders, and improving our services.
        \n
        \nLog Data:
        \n
        \nWhen you access the Service by or through a mobile device, we may collect certain
        information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use,
        your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating
        system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use and other statistics ("Log Data").
        \n
        \nIn addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect,
        monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service\'s
        functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies
        addressing how they use such information.
        \n
        \nCookies:
        \n
        \nCookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique
        identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device.
        We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you.
        \n
        \nYou can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being
        sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies,
        disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.
        \n
        \nIf you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and
        we recommend that you leave them turned on.
        \n
        \nDo Not Track Disclosure:
        \n
        \nWe do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your
        web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.You can enable or disable
        Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.
        \n
        \nService Providers:
        \n
        \nWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide
        the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in
        analyzing how our Service is used.
        \nThese third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific
        tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other
        purpose.
        \n
        \nCompliance With Laws:
        \n
        \nWe will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or
        if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable
        requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.
        \n
        \nBusiness Transaction:
        \n
        \nIf OrbitFingers is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal
        Information may be transferred as a business asset. In such cases, we will provide notice
        before your Personal Information is transferred and/or becomes subject to a different
        Privacy Policy.
        \n
        \nSecurity:
        \n
        \nThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement
        and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices
        appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from
        unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.
        \nHowever, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of
        electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of
        the Personal Information we have collected from you.
        \n
        \nInternational Transfer:
        \n
        \nYour information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained
        on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental
        jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
        \n
        \nIf you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please
        note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and
        process it there.
        \n
        \nYour consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information
        represents your agreement to that transfer.
        \n
        \nLinks To Other Sites:
        \n
        \nOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on
        a third party link, you will be directed to that third party\'s site. We strongly advise you
        to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
        \n
        \nWe have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies
        or practices of any third party sites or services.
        \n
        \nChildren\'s Privacy:
        \n
        \nOnly persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Our Service does not
        address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").
        \n
        \nWe do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13.
        If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with
        Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal
        Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take
        steps to remove that information from our servers.
        \n
        \nChanges To This Privacy Policy:
        \n
        \nThis Privacy Policy is effective as of July 18, 2017 and will remain in effect except with
        respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately
        after being posted on this page.
        \nWe reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should
        check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any
        modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the
        modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
        \n
        \nIf we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through
        the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
        \n
        \nContact Us:
        \n
        \nIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at
        orbitfingers.poloapps@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="tou_actual">Terms and Conditions:
        \n
        \n1. Introduction
        \n
        \nThese Standard Terms and Conditions written here shall manage your use of this software.
        These Terms will be applied fully and affect to your use of this OrbitFingers. By using this
        Application, you agreed to accept all terms and conditions written in here.
        You must not use this Application if you disagree with any of these Standard Terms and
        Conditions.
        \n
        \nDue to possible offensive language on the message board Users below 13 years old are not
        allowed to Register.
        \n
        \n2. Intellectual Property Rights
        \n
        \nOther than the content you own, under these Terms, PoloApps  owns all the intellectual
        property rights and materials contained in OrbitFingers or PoloApps.com.
        \nYou are granted limited license only for purposes of viewing the material contained on
        OrbitFingers or PoloApps.com.
        \n
        \n3. Restrictions
        \n
        \nYou are specifically restricted from all of the following:
        \n
        \n * publishing any OrbitFingers material in any other media;
        \n * selling, sub-licensing and/or otherwise commercializing any OrbitFingers material;
        \n * using this software in any way that is or may be damaging to the Mobile Application or
        Website;
        \n * using this software in any way that impacts user access to OrbitFinger Servers.
        \n * using this software contrary to applicable laws and regulations, or in any way may
        cause harm to OrbitFingers or PoloApps.com, or to any person or business entity;
        \n * using this software to engage in any advertising or marketing.
        \n
        \nCertain areas of this software are restricted from being access by you and PoloApps may
        further restrict access by you to any areas of this Application or related Website, at any
        time, in absolute discretion. Your password for this Application is hashed in the database
        and is kept confidential and you must maintain confidentiality as well. Usernames however
        are not confidential as the Top 5 Usernames are publicly displayed.
        \n
        \n4. Your Content
        \n
        \nIn this Application\'s Terms and Conditions, “Your Content” shall mean any audio, video
        text, images or other material you choose to display on this Application or Website. By
        displaying Your Content, you grant PoloApps a non-exclusive, worldwide irrevocable, sub
        licensable license to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate and distribute it in any and
        all media.
        \n
        \nYour Content must be your own and must not be invading any third-party’s rights. PoloApps
        reserves the right to remove any of Your Content from this Application or Website at any
        time without notice.
        \n
        \n5. No Warranties
        \n
        \nThis Software is provided “as is,” with all faults, and PoloApps express no
        representations or warranties, of any kind related to this Software or Website or the
        materials contained on here. Also, nothing contained on this Application or Website shall be
        interpreted as advising you.
        \n
        \n6. Limitation of Liability
        \n
        \nIn no event shall PoloApps, nor any of its officers, directors and employees, shall be
        held liable for anything arising out of or in any way connected with your use of this
        Website whether such liability is under contract. PoloApps, including its officers,
        directors and employees shall not be held liable for any indirect, consequential or special
        liability arising out of or in any way related to your use of this Application.
        \n
        \n7. Indemnification
        \n
        \nYou hereby indemnify to the fullest extent PoloApps from and against any and/or all
        liabilities, costs, demands, causes of action, damages and expenses arising in any way
        related to your breach of any of the provisions of these Terms.
        \n
        \n8. Severability
        \n
        \nIf any provision of these Terms is found to be invalid under any applicable law, such
        provisions shall be deleted without affecting the remaining provisions herein.
        \n
        \n9. Variation of Terms
        \n
        \nPoloApps is permitted to revise these Terms at any time as it sees fit, and by using this
        Application you are expected to review these Terms on a regular basis.
        \n
        \n10. Assignment
        \n
        \nPoloApps is allowed to assign, transfer, and subcontract its rights and/or obligations
        under these Terms without any notification. However, you are not allowed to assign, transfer
        , or subcontract any of your rights and/or obligations under these Terms.
        \n
        \n11. Entire Agreement
        \n
        \nThese Terms constitute the entire agreement between PoloApps and you in relation to your
        use of this Application, and supersede all prior agreements and understandings.
        \n
        \n12. Governing Law And Jurisdiction
        \n
        \nThese Terms will be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the State
        of CA, and you submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts
        located in CA for the resolution of any disputes.
        \n
    </string>
</resources>